{
    "id": "bdb2d94179dd432dad7f97d0997fd8ba",
    "title": "Complete the given passage",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "5713a324e79a48aba84b815bdfa58190",
            "title": "Complete The Given Passage",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "India .....................…… with many historical places and monuments.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "studded",
                        "is studding",
                        "is studded"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Agra ……………. an important place among them.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "occupy",
                        "occupies",
                        "is occupied"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The famous Taj Mahal ………………. this city.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is immortalizing",
                        "had immortalized",
                        "has immortalized"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "It was my long cherished dream to visit Taj Mahal and it ..................... last month when the school ..................... a trip to Agra.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "fulfilled, organized",
                        "has fulfilled, organized",
                        "was fulfilled, organized"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Taj Mahal ....................... one of the most famous buildings in the world.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "was",
                        "has been"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It .......................... situated on the River Yamuna.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "was",
                        "is"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Its four minarets, the tombs and the white marble ...................... it the most beautiful building in the world.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "make",
                        "makes",
                        "is making"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Poets ..................... it.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "had praised",
                        "have praised"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Common people ..................... it.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "adore",
                        "adorn",
                        "adoring"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Lovers of art from all over the world ......................... it.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "visit",
                        "visiting",
                        "were visiting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}